Alvic R. Comighud

1078 Juana Osmeña Ext., Cebu City, Philippines +63 933 4459425

Date of Birth: May 20, 1983

Online Portfolio: www.coroflot.com/alvicgraphics Email Address: alviccomighud@gmail.com

Summary

With over six years experience in Graphic Designing, I have detailed knowledge and experience in using the latest program in computer designing such as Adobe Photoshop CS6, Illustrator CS6 and InDesign CS6. I possess extensive experience in the area of design, prints and creative skills for advertising, web designing and promotional materials for various companies and businesses.

Objective

I am looking for a Graphic Designing role that involves conceptualizing design and development responsibilities through the use of designing softwares.

Education

June 2000 - October 2005 Bachelor of Fine Arts - major in Interior Design

University of San Carlos, Philippines

June 1996 - March 2000 Completed Secondary Education

University of Southern Philippines Foundation. Philippines

Employment History

Fine Resolutions Graphic Design Services
JL Building Room 4-A Avila St. Capitol Site Cebu City
May 2010 - June 2012

We are under Cactus Design and Marketing it's a German based company that designs greeting cards as well as gift ideas that is distributed to countries in Europe and America.

Graphic Designer

Responsibilities:

- Design Greeting Cards for anniversaries, birthdays, baptism, holiday seasons and everyday cards for German market.
- Create ideas for gift items and seasonal products such as key chains, bookmarks.
- Create concept and sample layouts base on knowledge of layout principles and aesthetic design concepts.
- Design paper bags for business or store use, personal use, customized and for gifts.
- Design printed paper wrappers for gifts.

Go Large Graphics Inc. Rabaya St. Talisay City 6045, Philippines 2006 - May 2010

Go Large Graphics Inc. has been at the forefront of offering large format prints services to clients Since 2002. Products range from outdoor print, indoor durable print, photographic print, wide format lamination and laser print services

OIC Graphic Designer

Responsibilities:

- Responsible for printing paper materials (TP paper, canvas, opaque stickers, high gloss Paper, C2S140 papers, Baklits and Heavyweight papers) on a window environment.
- Determine appropriate and arrangement of illustrative material and copy, and select style and size on a windows environment.
- Use computer software to generate new images.
- Mark up, paste and assemble final layouts to prepare for printing production.
- Review final layouts for tarpaulins, opaque stickers, perforated stickers, panaflex, clear Stickers and black & white materials and necessary improvements as needed.
- Discuss with clients to determine preferred layout design needed.
- Restores pictures and develop design for birthdays, events, ID's, announcements, posters, Banners, billboards, streamers, brochures, and other promotional events.

REFERESS:

- Lyralen Inso
 Graphic Designer
 Del Monte Foods
 FZE Dubai, UAE
 +971 55 9960095 / +971 554688190
- Anna Yap
 Graphic Designer
 GMASCO,Al Futtaim Group
 Orient Bldg. Al Badia Business Center, Dubai, UAE +971504884476
- Reyman Jude Rubin
 Senior Graphic Designer
 Tradekings Limited
 Nampundwe Rd. Light Industrial Area Lusaka, Zambia +260 97199919